<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Soil Nutrient Detector</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="npk_refers_to_the_three_essential_nutrients_required_for_plant_growth_nitrogen_n_phosphorus_p_and_potassium_k_nitrogen_n_is_crucial_for_plant_foliage_development_aiding_in_the_formation_of_chlorophyll_and_promoting_vibrant_green_leaves_phosphorus_p_supports_root_development_flowering_and_fruiting_by_facilitating_energy_transfer_within_the_plant_and_aiding_in_the_production_of_dna_and_rna_potassium_k_helps_regulate_water_uptake_promotes_disease_resistance_and_enhances_overall_plant_vigor">NPK refers to the three essential nutrients required for plant growth: nitrogen (N), phosphorus (P), and potassium (K). Nitrogen (N) is crucial for plant foliage development, aiding in the formation of chlorophyll and promoting vibrant green leaves. Phosphorus (P) supports root development, flowering, and fruiting by facilitating energy transfer within the plant and aiding in the production of DNA and RNA. Potassium (K) helps regulate water uptake, promotes disease resistance, and enhances overall plant vigor.</string>
    <string name="para1">NPK levels provides valuable insights into the nutrient composition of soil, aiding in optimal plant growth and health.NPK refers to the three essential nutrients required for plant growth: nitrogen (N), phosphorus (P), and potassium (K).</string>
    <string name="para2">-> Nitrogen (N) is crucial for plant foliage development, aiding in the formation of chlorophyll and promoting vibrant green leaves.
        \n\n-> Phosphorus (P) supports root development, flowering, and fruiting by facilitating energy transfer within the plant and aiding in the production of DNA and RNA. \n\n-> Potassium (K) helps regulate water uptake, promotes disease resistance, and enhances overall plant vigor.</string>
    <string name="para3">A NPK soil sensor helps determine the levels of these nutrients in the soil, allowing for precise fertilization strategies tailored to the specific needs of plants. By ensuring the appropriate balance of nitrogen, phosphorus, and potassium, growers can optimize plant growth, yield, and resilience while minimizing environmental impact and resource waste.</string>
</resources>